thesportshq.com 2015-03-18

# The Sports HQ - PrivacyPolicy

##### Privacy Policy 

S247 PLC is committed to respecting your privacy. The following sets forth our information gathering and usage practices for this Web site. 

##### Information Gathered At This Web Site 

S247 PLC automatically collects anonymous information about usage of this Web site. When you visit this Web site, we identify the browser you are using, the internet service provider you are using, the pages you visit at our site, and other information of this kind. None of this information identifies you personally. 

To facilitate shopping on our site and to speed up browsing we may collect certain anonymous information from users of this Web site by using "cookies." A cookie is a small file that your browser stores on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. Cookies help you move more quickly through our Web site. If you do not want to accept cookies, you can set your browser to refuse all cookies or to alert you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie from this Web site, some parts of this Web site may perform less efficiently and some parts may not perform at all. For instance, it is not possible to purchase products from our web site without using cookies. 

On certain pages of this web site you may voluntarily provide us with names, addresses, phone numbers, fax numbers, e-mail addresses, credit card numbers and similar information. S247 PLC respects your privacy and the importance you place on your personal information. We have taken every precaution with the security of your credit card numbers, address, and other information as it is sent across the Internet. S247 PLC takes precautions to protect your personal information, including allowing access only to those S247 PLC employees with a need to know and using available technology and encryption to provide a secure environment and to prevent unauthorized access.. 

##### Internal Use of Information 

We store on our server the information you provide us, as well as the anonymous information that is automatically collected. We may use the anonymous information to understand better how this Web site is being used. 

We may use personal information that you have voluntarily provided to provide the goods or services that you have requested, to adjust this Web site to your personal preferences, to send to you via e-mail or postal mail newsletters, new product announcements or other information that we feel may be of value to you, and for other similar business purposes. 

##### Sharing of Information with Third Parties 

S247 PLC will not share your information with any third parties. Your security is as important to us as it is to you.. 

##### Opting Out 

You may at any time opt out of receiving further communications via e-mail. When you receive an e-mail from us, you will be given the option of replying with an instruction to delete your name from our e-mail list. Please note, however, that you may be added again to our e-mail list if you subsequently participate in other promotions or submit further personal information at this Web site. 

##### Modifications of Our Policy 

From time to time, we may modify our Privacy Policy. Such modifications will be effective on the date that we post the modified Policy on our Web site. 

##### Contact Information 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or about this Web site in general, please contact us at [privacy@sportsplc.com](mailto:privacy@sportsplc.com)
